you just couldn't resist, could you?
the allure of magic was far too strong
mastering gregtech power isn't enough for you
only absolute power will suffice
magical infusion
bloody sacrifice
a witchery brew
you want it all, you need it all
but where does it begin
right here of course
congratulations
the Hogwarts letter you've been waiting for all your life has just arrived
welcome to the beginners guide to gregtech new horizons
this is episode six, magic
here we are in the new base
recognize the design?
today we cover the basics of Thaumcraft, Botania, witchery and blood magic
enough to get you going and on your way towards the many delights magic can offer you in GTNH
oh right this is GTNH
which means magic is way more useful and well integrated than anything you've ever seen
and also a bit more complicated than usual
as always, first things first
keep in mind that all this is optional at least for now
but has huge benefits
and like everything else, the earlier you get them
the more payoff they have
it's still a bit early in overall progression to go too nuts with magic
but now that you have aluminum
and a while to wait to get enough stuff to make the power system you planned after last episode
you can get started
and if you've gotten a bit lucky with loot
you can take it pretty far
the long and short is you need stainless steel
16 ingots in total to take you through everything you're gonna see here
and a couple of eyes of ender
which you can get from villagers before you have machines that can make them in hv
even if you did get lucky with loot
this guide will take you until the end of MV to complete
and you'll need some MV machines
so keep that in mind
and that's far from all you need
you certainly won't be finishing magic progression with just that
but this is the beginner's guide
so let's begin
it all starts with thaumcraft
it's no coincidence that this is the first magic mod the quest book calls out
to get started on any of the other magic mods
you'll need to make some progress with thaumcraft
it might appear that getting aluminum will unlock the quest chapter
but if you didn't unlock it when you went to the twilight
what you actually need is a quest way back in the "so it begins" chapter
what's that
if you can't find silverwood or greatwood trees
buy the saplings from the quest book
if you haven't been doing the side quests
you might have to do a few now to get the right coins
either way, you can start thinking about your first wand
you've been to the twilight to do some mining
now it's time to go back and do some fighting
oh, and more mining
before you go boss hunting
you might want to pause for a bit
and check out the introductory quests in the thaumcraft chapter
firstly, ironwood is handy if you didn't grind out the cobalt pickaxe head already
and the armor is pretty good too, at least for now
the magic map is also worth grabbing now
since it'll point you directly to the bosses you need to slay
speaking of, there are lots of them
but for early progression
you only need to kill two
the Naga and the Lich king
the Naga isn't super dangerous
if you have a few extra hearts
you can probably run right at them
and start swinging with a decent sword
or shooting with your carbon limb crossbow
and if you have it in you
kill a few
to make the first wand, you only need two scales
but you'll need to craft an upgrade before you can make a wand that uses the next boss drop
if you want to stop after the Naga
and do the next part later
feel free
but the Lich is only slightly more complicated
pillar up to the boss room
it should be pretty obvious which one it is
and break straight in
while the boss is waking up
block off the staircase so the mobs below don't wander into the Arena
a creeper explosion at this moment would be most untimely
draw your sword and start swinging
this time to keep the zombies at Bay
and try to reflect the flying interpoles (?) back at the boss to remove the shields that are circling them
once they're gone, slay on slayer
if you get pinched
hide in one of the side rooms or just bail out of the room
a few red hearts can be handy for instant regen if you've gotten any from your blaze farm
again, a couple of boss kills can be worth it
but by the time you're using Lich bones to make wands
you'll be ready to make a bit of salas mudus to craft the bones using the trophy
before you leave the twilight
grab a couple stacks worth of every shard ore
ore doubling these is painfully slow
so you might want to start by smelting them directly
if so, consider grabbing the silky jewel reward from the twilight forest quest
either way get plenty
and once you're home
crafting the wand is elementary
ollendor delights (?)
now the snowball can start rolling
right click a bookshelf with the wand to get your thaumonicon
right click a table with the wand to get your arcane worktable
right click a cauldron with the wand to get your crucible
right click two tables with describing tools to get your research station
and then use your shards to make the thaumometer
you've acquired the basics your trip to Hogsmeade has concluded
and just like that the Hogwarts express has dropped you off
and you're in your first lesson
so pay close attention
thaumcraft research is a minigame that spends points to complete a chain of aspects
aspects are the core elements of magic that everything in the game is composed of
everything is made up of different aspects
and every research is made up of different sequences of aspects
that need to be connected via other aspects that share part of their makeup
before we worry too much about that
you need to accumulate some aspects
the quest book has a nice list of what to scan for all the aspects soon
don't worry too much about what you've unlocked
just scan the list of things for now
you can either hold the thaumometer and look at things
or hover over items in your inventory
as the quest book indicates, the first set of things needs to be scanned in order
don't skip any
scan as many of the other things in the list as you have or can find
and be prepared to make things
or go kill mobs for loot
or go hunting
if you get a message that you're missing knowledge to scan an item
skip it, and circle back to it next time you see that message
this is a one time effort to unlock knowledge of all the aspects
so knuckle down and get it done
for the tainted anything item
your best bet is finding a tainted lands biome
you might be traveling quite a while to find one
use the biome compass
and find a magical forest while you're out if you haven't already
once you find the tainted lands
scan something tainted then bail
and do not chunkload this area
if you base near it, move
no matter how time consuming it'll be
you have just observed the future of your base and the entire world if you aren't careful
all consumed in tainted
which is why i don't recommend experimenting with the method the quest book recommends
unless you have some experience
now that you have all the aspects
scan literally everything you own
you can review them in NEI to see which items produce those aspects when scanned
or run through the alchemical furnace
take another look at your research station now too
all the aspects are there
ready to be used for the research minigame
each has a number representing how many points worth that aspect you have scanned
to accumulate more
you need to scan new items that contain that aspect type
in general you'll want to scan basically every new thing you encounter in craft going forward
and go back and scan every single thing you possess
you'll probably notice that you accumulate more of a couple particular aspects than you do anything else
due to how many unique machines you have laying around to scan
ordo and instrumentum
if benzene is the metaphor for power
ordo and instrumentum are the metaphor for thaumcraft research
aside from the primal aspects
every other aspect is made up from two other aspects
for example, air plus ordo makes motus
with scribe tools and paper in your inventory
click on non-research in the thaumonicon to get a research sheet
and stick it in the table with the scribe tools
the way the research minigame works is by connecting the aspects that start on the research sheet using other aspects that are made up from them
motus can be placed beside ordo
because motus is composed of ordo
air can be placed on the other side of motus
because motus is also composed of air
now we have a link between ordo and air via motus
to complete the research
you simply connect all the aspects using the same idea
both different aspects depending on what the research starts with
make sense?
after you play with it for a bit
you may notice that almost every research can be completed by first converting the starting aspects into ordo or instrumentum
and then alternating between the two to bridge gaps
things should be loaded with both of these things
and might struggle to get anything else in large supply
this is the way
as you unlock research
you'll notice that some of them are labeled forbidden knowledge
with varying degrees of severity
this is thaumcraft warp
or a way to represent how much dark magic you've dealt into
the more you do the bigger the number and the bigger the consequences
until you're spawning withers in your base
the starting effects range from goofy to quirky to annoying
and the later effects can be downright evil
don't worry about it too much to begin, don't get carried away
the quest book will lead you to how to deal with it in the advanced thaumcraft chapter
but not soon
now about your taint
uh
anyway one of the ways you end up with taint is by introducing too much flux in the world
right, another term
think about flux as excess magic
if you get a bunch of junk and put it in the crucible
and it leaves a bunch of extra junk after making the thing you want
you get flux
you might see this as purple goo that overflows out
a tiny bit is okay
just clean it up by placing blocks on it
too much flux is really, really, really bad
like creating an infinitely spreading tainted lands biome in your base pad
it would take being super careless to end up there
but if you're new to the mod, it's not impossible
there are ways to cheese using the microblocks and trapdoors
but this is a beginner's guide
so we're gonna focus on getting a safe crafting the way the mod provides
quick notes on the thaumonicon and research
the research is split up into pages or chapters
or whatever you want to call them
basic information is where it all begins
and most if not all of these are worth grabbing right away to make the research points go further
and make sure you don't accidentally destroy a node while you're charging your wand
we'll get to that in a sec
thaumaturgy is all about the basics of making and using wands
alchemy is about crafting with the crucible and metal transmutation
artifice is about the tools and utility items
tons of good stuff in there including infusion
and there's lots more chapters
some odd specific ones like blood magic and Botania
and some just containing more cool and useful stuff
some you won't unlock until you go insane, end game
covering everything in this book would take hours
so we aren't doing that here
the main point is you don't need every research
not even every research in a chapter
but trust me you might want them
everything we're going to cover is in the chapters i just mentioned
so start there
one more thing on research
if you know an item you want ahead of time
say the boots of the traveler for example
you'll see that you don't have the research
one of the tricky parts about thaumcraft is it's hard to know what research unlocks the research you actually want
not in GTNH
hovering over the research name tells you what the parent researches are
and which chapter they're in
which can sometimes be a direct path
if you can't see the prerequisite research either
there's a research cheat sheet in the wiki, linked below
it takes some bouncing around
but in the end
you can find where all the research you need is
and where to unlock it
you can also turn on a mod option to allow you to see the recipes for items you haven't researched yet
mod options
thaumcraft NEI additions
general
show locked recipes
but fair warning
it gets really hard to tell what you've actually researched if it's on
useful though
now going forward i'm gonna assume you simply have all the research you need
if you finish most of what's in the first four chapters of the thaumonicon
you will
to get anywhere with thaumcraft
you need the infusion altar
and to use it, you need jars of essentia
to get those, you need an alchemical furnace and some arcane alembics (?)
and to craft those you need vis in your wand
grab yourself some goggles of revealing
oh wait
your 20 capacity wand is way too garbage for that
we'll fix that momentarily
instead grab your thaumometer and start wandering
you're looking for nodes
which will appear as bright balls of light until you get up close
scan them and you can see which aspects they're made of
they'll mostly be primal aspects
which is good, because that's what you need
searching at night can make them easier to find
they have a slight light signature similar to the beehives
you need at least one of every primal aspect in enough quantity to fill your wand
and the more the better
you shouldn't have to wander too far to get just that
right click with the wand to charge it
and be careful not to drain the nodes empty and destroy them
this wand is bad
your first priority is making a wand good enough to get the goggles of revealing
and ultimately the rest of the vis discount gear you can make early
and stop yourself from breaking nets
since you got lucky with stainless steel
you can jump right to the iron cap greatwood wand
which bumps the vis capacity up to 40
and if you have the node preserver research
will prevent you from breaking nodes
unless you're sneaking while charging
grab the goggles of revealing
find some more nodes
much more easily this time
and get to work on the bewitched robe and bewitched leggings and thaumaturge's boots
to max out your vis discount for crafting
you'll need the spinning wheel and some thaumium
it's time to talk alchemy
the very first thing you want from your crucible is nitor
so craft it up by tossing in four torches, two coal and a piece of glowstone
that was your first perfect craft
goodbye fire
the next thing you want is a large supply of balance shards and thaumium, thaumcraft base metal
toss in four of each shard
finishing with four air shards
and then five iron ingots and five air crystal powder
you should end up with four balance shards
five thaumium and five air shards
with no excess essentia in the crucible
it works the same way with any crystal powder
and with the shards in any order
if you're tired of running all over the place to charge your wand
you'll probably want some primal shrooms
you need to find vishrooms in a magical forest
which hopefully you found long ago
or the biome compass can lead you to easily
get quite literally as many as you can
and buy them from the quest book
a pumpkin and two tiny piles of stone dust and a vishroom
get you a primal
and that's free vis
the watering can works on him as well
no matter how much time you spend doing this
it's less than you would spend roaming node to node
and with thaumium and all the vis you need
you can start using the alchemical furnace with a couple of arcane alembics
to break down items into their component essentias
and store it all in jars
any combustible can fuel it
but aluminum makes it drain essentia faster
you can continue to use a regular crucible setup when you have perfect crafts
like for nitors, balance shards and thaumium
and now aluminum with three coal three tiny piles of stone dust and a coal dust
once there's essentia in the alembic
slap a label on it
so we'll only accept that type
you can remove them
but this keeps the pipes from making things weird
essentia pipes are super goofy
but for our purposes
just pipe straight into a jar from the alembic
you can label the jars too
and Voila, restoring essentia for future use
and there's no need to wait
if you make a couple of alchemical constructs and stick them on top of crucible
now you got a system for perfect ratio Alchemy
just plug your jars into the sides
and Bingo Bango
you can also and should also upgrade your wand again
this time to the satin entwined greatwood wand
the quest is either or (?) and satin is better
so go for that
slap on your bewitch robes and leggings your goggles and your thaumaturge boots
and get your final wand upgrade for now
the gold banded greatwood scepter
you needed that 50 capacity wand specifically for the primal charm to make the next wand
this is how a wand progression works from here
so get used to it
with this wand you can start bringing home nodes in jars
check the research
shortening your vis recharge even more
and preparing for advanced thaumaturgy
and finally, the infusion altar
this is basically the end of the line for us for now
with this, the rest of thaumcraft and all the other magic mods are open to you
not to mention the best animation in the history of the game
hopefully you found a villager willing to trade you an ender pearl
if not you're waiting until HV for this
which is a big time bummer
because the boots of the traveler are so much better earlier than that
work on those first
and rejoice at how much more convenient getting around is about to become
the recipes show the ingredients around the center
and they don't need to be in perfect order
but they do need to be balanced on the pedestals
if there are four items to the left, put four on the right, and so on
some recipes don't have perfect balance
which can be a little jarring to look at
but they still work
every recipe also has a stability value
once you get the arcane abacus
you can have the recipe laid out on the pedestals
and the abacus will tell you the instability of the recipe
and the stability of your altar
sadly you can't get this until close to the end of MV
when you can get your first hv circuits
before that just overload on stability boosters
there are lots of blocks that can boost stability
and they all tell you that
the easiest way is probably quicksilver blocks
they make a symmetrical pattern under your altar
you can go another couple layers below as well
throw down some skulls or candles
and just make sure the pattern they have is symmetrical for the maximum boost
once you have some stability going
lay out a crafting recipe
and right click the matrix at the center with your wand to start the craft
after the boots of the traveler
it's up to you just how far down the rabbit hole you want to go
so now you know how to get into thaumcraft
the only question left is, why
beyond unlocking the other magic mods and finishing the pack that is well here's the thing
yeah worth
there's also the nano suit boots of the traveler
and the goggles of revealing to go with the rest of your nano suit
which are amazing
and a lot of players, including me, hardline the thaumcraft restorer (?)
which can repair, among other things, the oblivion frames
a crucial early item for bee progression
and the flight potion that grants create a flight
yeah you want this
short bit on bees
they are absurdly good in GTNH for everything
and i mean everything
they're reason enough to get as far as we've gone in the guide
they're the basis of my resource generation
and the power generation in my own world
outrageously good
if you want to learn how to do bees
check out Aditya's guide
by far the most exhaustive and useful guide on GTNH bee that exists
you'll be glad you invested in magic, i'll say that
and if you want to take thaumcraft farther than we've gone here
you'll need better wands
which threefold's GTNH spreadsheet has some amazing information on
as well as information on which items give the clearest source of essentia
routes to both are linked below
so with thaumcraft progression in the bag
you can move on to the other magic mods
all of which have conveniences that are nearly as good or better
how about some herbology next?
Botania has its own research chapter
which i'll assume you've completed as relevant here
it also has its own book, the Lexica Botania
which you should a hundred percent read
great mod book it must be said
cheers vasquez
you can actually get into Botania without doing thaumcraft
but it would be a little painful
no matter what you'll start by wandering the twilight forest
looking for caves that contain shimmering mushrooms
you'll be converting them to flowers using Alchemy
and like with most things
the more you collect the easier it will be to snowball
so keep at it for a bit
but you'll also unlock ways to duplicate them
also through alchemy
or you might have already
the Petal apothecary is the crafting table of Botania
and the first thing you want to make are pure daisies
to use the apothecary
fill with water
drop recipe items in
then toss seeds in to complete the craft
shift right click with an empty hand to repeat the whole recipe
a handful of pure daisies will do it
hop them down and surround each one with logs or stone
and in a jiff, they'll convert to living wood and living rock
with living wood in hand
make your first wand of the forest with a couple of petals and the colors of your preference
now you're ready to rock
living rock
we're Gonna speed run mana generation here
so buckle in
make the diluted mana pool
and get ready to trash it almost immediately
to start, you'll have to use dayblooms and nightshades
one generates mana during the day and the other at night
they die, so make sure you get your money's worth
place a mana spreader nearby
and shift right click on the flower then the spreader while in bind mode to link them
you'll see a green check mark indicating it was successful
and a nice particle effect showing the flow
do the same to the spreader and link it to the mana pool
as soon as you get the visual indicator
that you can make mana steel by dropping a steel ingot into the pool
do it
then immediately replace the diluted pool with a real mana pool
you might even salvage an extra bit of free mana from your first flowers
the next flower you want is the Emdoflame
which can eat combustibles
and whose only real difficulty is the burning blossoms from the nether
with a 30 second timer and a dropper
you can set up an Emdoflame to produce mana for a good long while
you can easily scale the same setup to a bunch of Emdoflames
long term, the thermolilly (?)
paired with an ever burner and cycling buckets into droppers
and otherwise working exactly the same way as the emdoflame setup
using a timer set to five minutes
is going to produce massive amounts of mana
to get that one though you need the runic altar
luckily, you have thaumcraft infusion
so this is no big deal
you get the prismarine shards by dropping nether quartz in a mana pool with the alchemy catalyst underneath the pool
a bit more research and crafting
and they're all yours
once you have it
place a couple of spreaders next to your mana pool
and point them at the altar
right click the recipe items onto the altar
let the mana build up until you get a sweet lightning animation
then toss living rock on the top
and right click with the wand
bazinga
you're runicing
so why Botania
first of all
it looks cool and makes for awesome thematic decoration
secondly though is cheap tiered glass
and an excellent gregtech tool material
mana glass is way easier to make than the equivalent gregtech glass
which you'll need for some of the upcoming multi blocks
and mana steel and after EV terra steel are incredible tool materials for their time
not to mention the Botania tools themselves
which are insane
oh and fantastic potions, resource duplication and transmutation
the single longest crafting recipe in the entire game
and if you get through it all
the most Epic boss battle music of all time
what's not to love
next up, potions with professor Snape
it's time for witchery
and it begins with a bit of farming
actually hoeing the grass away from water to get the witchery seeds
farm them up
and beware the mandrakes
using the crossbow to break the plant
and immediately shoot the little guy tends to work
but if not, just make the earphones
secure the cauldron, the witch's oven and a bunch of clay jars
and start making all the odors and such
thapplings (?) might actually be a problem
you haven't needed them until now
enjoy
light a fire under the cauldron
fill it with three buckets of water
and toss in the items the quest book suggests one at a time
to get yourself some mutandis
and use the mutandis on grass or flowers
until you get three witchery saplings
Rowan, alder and hawthorn
then you might need a bit
farm some wood, and leave a couple of trees grown as well
the next thing you'll need is the witchery altar
and it gets more power the more variety of nature is around it
so max out the different trees and flowers
there are a few other things you can use to upgrade the ultra power as well
toss your own skull on there
candelabra you made with the altar
and the chalice from the quest
if you take the redstone soup award
you can upgrade the chalice right away and make it better
you need 5450 ultra power for the short term goal
and if you're way short
the Dragon egg will take you over the top
though that's a mission of its own
try some more nature first
to follow the quest book to the thing you actually want
you'll need to have a nightmare and visit the spirit world
grab yourself a kettle
light a fire under it
and craft up some brews to sleep
drink a sip of flight potion and night vision potion before you drink the brew
you can't bring anything with you
and you'll want to make this quick, trust me
immediately grab as much to serve cotton as you can find while dodging monsters
and then let one kill you
you're done with this dimension if you want
grab the spinning wheel and the distillery
luckily, your wand is up to snuff for the craft
since you need 80 vis capacity
now you can make the witch's robes
and most importantly diamond vapor
which unlocks the main reason you'd do witchery at all
biome changing potions
absolutely amazing for all those bees that have particular requirements for jubilation (?)
did i mention bees are awesome?
just grab a biome page
and toss the items the quest book suggests into the cauldron to brew
completely worth the effort on its own
to reiterate, these are absurd
but if that's not enough for you
you can get some insane potions from witchery
and the other were infusion
which is a legit substitute for the home command
oh and werewolves you can be a werewolf
there's lots of goofy stuff for multiplayer too
and lastly, you need those attuned stones you've been using to get into blood magic
and so we've arrived at the dark arts with he who must not be named
a joint enrollment class at Durmstrang
fair warning, getting into blood magic is 100 percent going to increase your warp
so if you plan to do it early
plan not to have a way to deal with that
unless you've gone completely nuts with other warpy research
you'll be fine
but your soul is forfeit
the blood altar uses items from thaumcraft and witchery and some others
and requires the implosion compressor
which you can't make until you get HV circuits at the end of MV
and which you otherwise probably wouldn't make until you're thinking about the tier 1 Rocket
but you should for this
and since you only need two double compressed cobble
the powder barrels work fine
the blood altar is a multi block with six tiers
and we'll be rushing the tier 3 altar here
the tier 1 altar is just the block itself
and to fill it with blood at the start
you'll need the dagger of sacrifice
it's time for some bloodletting
this would be a massive literally painful grind if it weren't for your preparation
you've got all the options you need for regeneration potions
and if those don't suit you
a stockpile of red hearts from your blaze farm for instant regen
you might even have some industrious bees giving the regen effect constantly
with nothing, prepare for pure pain
with enough regen, prepare for easy street (?)
craft yourself a ton of blank slates
you can use a hopper or conduit to do 10 at a time
for the cost of a full altar of blood
and a filtered EnderIO conduit for extracting only once you get the rune you want
and nothing else about slate crafting gets better than it is right now
assuming you have dank (?) regen until you get a ton of upgrade runes
which you can't make until you have a tier 3 altar and a ton of slates
A TON OF SLATES
and of course, the tier 1 blood orb
once you have it
right click while holding it to bind it
then stick it back in the altar and let it soak up some blood
you now have an LP network
the divination sigil will tell you how much LP you have
and there are a bunch of other cool sigils too
it takes eight blank runes to upgrade the altar to tier 2
and snag your tier 2 orb while you're there
and another 20 to upgrade to tier 3
four blank slates per rune for a total of 112 slates
and that's before you can get any runes that improve blood generation
each tier of the altar adds a tier of slate
and you'll want a bunch of tier 2
and at least a handful of tier 3
besides the ones you need for the rune upgrades
yeah you're gonna need a lot of blood
the tier 3 altar also requires blood soak thaumium blocks
so i hope you stocked up earlier
and the tier 3 blood orb specifically requires 30 thousand blood
so using speed runes might hurt you
unless you grind out some augment and capacity runes too
no matter what, you need to invest in runes before you'll be successful in making the tier 3 orb
but you need titanium for that anyway
so you aren't making it now
and that means you have time to make the upgrade runes before the end of HV
which means you also have time for a little bit of blood Alchemy
after a bit more research
you can make the alchemist chemistry set
this thing has quite a few very useful recipes
but for now, you're after alchemy ingredients
simple catalyst
strengthen catalyst
Sanctus
Tenebrae
Incendium
Potentia
Aether
Terrae
and Aquasalus
there are a few more too
but with all these
you'll be free to make that big decision
self sacrifice or sacrifice
you're going to sit tight at this level of blood magic for a bit
so some self sacrifice runes are worth it
they'll speed up the finger pricking substantially
consider the glass dagger of sacrifice if you go this route
if you plan to use the well of suffering
which you will eventually no matter what
you're gonna want runes of sacrifice instead
the problem is you need a tier 4 altar for that
and that will require more thaumcraft progression than you've done
a lot more
the dangerous kind
from this point, the quest book does a decent job of walking you through things
they also start to overlap a bit
and get a little bit complicated
so we may circle back for another round of magic at some point later in the guide
let me know if that interests you
maddening frames
which you might be able to make now if you've already gotten into bees a bit
and is incredible for bee breeding
the well of suffering
for infinite blood generation
bound tools
unbreakable tools that obliterate entire veins in one swing
bound armor
that makes you nearly invincible
and looks sick
energy blasters
for firing off devastating energy attacks
and if you're able to put it all together
completely automated resource from blood magic meteors
interdimensional item transport using magic mirrors
and enough item intake to deal with everything you've got
and thaumic energetics
digital essentia storage and automation
magic is insane
and insanely underappreciated
GTNH is obviously a tech pack
there's a lot more than that under the hood
you got plenty to explore as you make more aluminum
repair your power system
and get yourself ready for the beast that is in MV
see you there for episode 7
你就是抵挡不了诱惑，不是吗？
魔法的诱惑太强烈了
掌握科技的力量对你来说还不够
只有绝对的力量才足够
神秘注魔
血腥献祭
巫术酿造
你想要这一切，你需要这一切
但是魔法从哪里开始呢？
当然就从这里开始
恭喜
你等了一辈子的霍格沃茨的入学通知刚刚到了
欢迎来到格雷科技-新视野初学者指南
第六集，魔法
我们到了新基地
这个设计还记得吗？
今天我们将涵盖神秘、植物魔法啊、巫术和血魔法的基础知识
这些知识足以让你继续发展，朝着魔法为你提供的许多快乐进发
哦，对了，这是GTNH
这意味着魔法比你见过的其他整合包都更有用，更与主线融合在一起
也比平时复杂一点
一如既往，要事第一
请记住，至少目前这一切都是可选的
但有巨大的回报
和其他东西一样，你越早得到它们
他们得到的回报就越多
现在就为魔法太着迷稍微有点太早
但现在你有铝了
还有一段空闲时间等材料足够来制造你计划的电力系统
源神，启动！
如果你在搜刮战利品箱上比较走运
你可以走得很远
总而言之，你需要不锈钢
只需16块不锈钢就能带你通过你将在这里看到的一切
还需要几个末影之眼
在你有HV机器制造它们之前，你可以从村民那里得到
即使你走了狗屎运
本指南将带你直到MV结束才能完成
你需要一些MV机器
所以记住这一点
这远非你所需要的
你肯定不会就这么走完魔法线
但这是新手引导
所以让我们开始吧
这一切都始于神秘时代
这就是为什么它是任务书里出现的第一个魔法mod
要想开始任何其他魔法mod
你需要在神秘上取得一些进展
书上写获得铝会解锁魔法章节
但是如果你去暮光森林的时候没有解锁它
你真正需要的是回到“由此开始”一章的任务
那是什么任务？
如果你找不到银木或宏伟之木
就从任务书中购买树苗
如果你没有做支线任务
你现在可能需要做一些才能获得硬币
不管怎样，你可以开始考虑你的第一根魔杖了
你已经去过暮色森林挖矿了
现在是时候回去杀怪了
哦，也要接着挖矿
在你去找boss之前
你可能想先等一下
并查看神秘章节中的介绍性任务
首先，如果你没有钴镐头，铁树是个不错的材料
盔甲也不赖，至少对现在而言
魔法地图也可以搞一份
因为它会直接指向你需要杀死的boss
说起来，boss其实有不少
但对于早期发展
你只需要杀两个
娜迦和巫妖王
娜迦并不是特别危险
如果你加了几颗额外的心
你可以直接冲过去
然后直接挥舞左剑（左键）
或者用你的碳臂弩射击
如果你有这种能力？
杀几个
要制作第一根魔杖，你只需要两个娜迦鳞片
但是你需要在制作一根使用下一个boss掉落的魔杖之前进行升级
如果你想在娜迦之后停下来
之后再往下推进
都可以
巫妖只是稍微复杂一点
顶上boss的房间
是哪一个应该很明显
直接踢门进入
趁boss亮血条的时候
堵住楼梯，这样下面的怪物就不会到场地里了
此时苦力怕爆炸有点不合适了
然后直接挥舞左剑（左键）
这次是为了阻止僵尸
并尝试将飞行的末影珍珠弹回boss以破除环绕护盾
一旦盾被破除，上去开砍
如果你被围住了
藏在旁边的房间里或者直接跳出房间
如果你从你的火焰人刷怪场得到了一些红心，它们可以作为方便的瞬间治疗药水
再说一次，杀几次boss是值得的
但是当你用巫妖骨头做魔杖的时候
你已经可以用世界盐来制作巫妖骨头了
在你离开暮色森林之前
挖几组各个种类碎片
矿石翻倍非常非常慢
所以你可能直接熔炼就完事了
如果是这样，考虑从暮色森林森林任务中获得丝绸珠宝奖励
不管怎样
一旦你回到家
制作魔杖就是最基本的
奥伦多快乐（？）
现在雪球可以开始滚动了
用法杖右键单击书架以获取你的魔导手册
用法杖右键单击一张台桌以获得你的奥术工作台
用法杖右键单击一个炼药锅以获得你的坩埚
用笔与墨右键单击两个台桌以获取你的研究台
然后用碎片制作魔导透镜
你已经掌握了基本的魔法知识（需要分行）
就这样，你从霍格沃茨特快上下来了
这是你的第一堂课
认真听讲
神秘研究是个小游戏，通过花费研究点来完成一些“要素链”
要素是神秘时代的核心元素，是一切事物的基本构成
每个事物都是由不同的要素组成的
每项研究都由一系列要素组成
我们要做的是将它们连接起来，中间是它们之间共有的组成要素
在我们太操心研究之前
你需要积累一些要素
任务书上有一个不错的列表，列出了要扫描的所有要素
不要太担心你解锁了什么
现在就看一眼清单
你可以拿着魔导透镜观察东西
或悬停在库存中的物品上
正如任务书所指出的，第一组东西需要按顺序扫
不要跳着扫
扫描列表中尽可能多你已经找到或者能找到的东西
并准备好搓一些东西
或者去杀怪物获得战利品
或者去打猎
如果你收到一条消息，说你缺少扫描物品的知识
跳过它，下次看到该消息时再回来看看
解锁所有要素只需要干一次就行
所以全力以赴完成它
对于腐化的任何物品
你最好的选择是找到一个腐化之地生物群系
你可能要探很长时间图才能找到一个
使用生物群系指南针
在你游历四方的时候再找一个魔法森林群系，如果你还没有见过的话
一旦你找到腐化之地
扫描受污染的东西然后就跑
不要加载这个区域
如果你基地就在旁边，移动（此处插入祥子移动jpg）
别管要花多久
如果你不小心处理腐化的话，你基地和整个世界未来就是刚刚那样
全部被腐化吞噬
这就是为什么我不建议尝试任务书推荐的方法
除非你已经有了经验
现在你解锁了所有的要素
扫描你拥有的所有东西
你可以在NEI中查看它们，以查看扫描时哪些物品包含这些要素
或者看看炼金炉配方
现在也再看看你的研究台
所有要素应该都在了
准备用于研究小游戏
每个要素都有数字，显示了你扫描了该要素的研究点
要多收集一些研究点
你需要扫描包含该要素的新物品
一般来说，你要扫描你在制作中得到的每一件新东西
以及回去扫描你所有已有的东西
你可能会注意到你积累的几个特定要素比其他的都多
因为你有特别多不同类型机器可以扫描
秩序和工具
如果苯代表了电力
秩序和工具则代表了神秘研究
除了原始要素
其他所有要素都是由另外两个要素组成的
例如，风加秩序是移动
在背包里放上笔与墨和纸
点击魔导手册中的未完成的研究获得研究笔记
把笔记，笔与墨放到研究台上
研究小游戏的玩法是，用由用组成的要素连接图中一开始就有的要素
移动可以放在秩序旁边
因为移动是由秩序组成的
气可以放在移动的另一边
因为移动也是由气组成的
现在我们通过移动找到了秩序和气之间的联系
要完成研究
你只需用这个思路连接所有要素
这两个不同的要素取决于研究的开始（？）
懂了吗？
在你玩了一会儿之后
你可能会注意到，几乎每项研究都可以通过首先将起始要素转换为秩序或工具来完成
然后在两者之间交替来搭桥
东西应该同时加载这两个东西
可能很难得到其他大量供应的东西。（？）
这就是方法（？）
当你解锁研究时
你会注意到其中一些有禁忌知识的标签
不同的知识后果不同
这就是扭曲
用来表示你使用了多少黑魔法的数值
你做的越多，数字越大，后果越严重
直到你的基地里生凋零了
一开始效果是愚蠢到古怪再到烦人
后来的效果可以是彻头彻尾的哈人
开始时不要太担心，不要忘乎所以
任务书将在后面的神秘章节教你中如何处理它
但是是后期的事了
现在关于你的污染
额
总之，污染的其中一个后果就是给这个世界带来了太多的通量。
对，另一个术语
把通量想象成多余的魔法
如果你把一堆垃圾放进坩埚
在做了你想要的东西后，它会留下一堆额外的垃圾。
你得到通量
你可能会认为这是溢出的紫色粘性物质
一点点没关系
只要在上面放块就可以清理了
太多的流量真的，真的，真的很糟糕
就像在你的基地创造一个无限蔓延的污染土地生物群落
如果你真的是太粗心了
但如果你是mod的新手，这并非不可能
有很多方法可以使用微块和活板门
但这是新手引导
所以我们要专注于按照mod提供的方式进行安全制作
关于thaumonomicon和研究的快速笔记
研究分为几页或几章
或者随便你怎么称呼他们
基本信息是一切的开始
如果不是所有这些都值得马上抓住，让研究点走得更远
并确保你在给魔杖充电时不会意外破坏节点
我们一会儿再谈这个
神学是关于制作和使用魔杖的基础知识
炼金术是关于用坩埚和金属蜕变来制作
技巧是关于工具和实用物品的
里面有很多好东西包括输液
还有很多章节
一些奇怪的特定的，比如血魔法和植物
有些只是包含更多很酷和有用的东西
有些你不会解锁，直到你疯了，结束游戏
涵盖这本书里的所有内容需要几个小时
所以我们不会在这里这样做
重点是你不需要每一项研究
甚至不是一章中的每一项研究
但相信我你可能会想要它们
我们要讨论的内容都在我刚才提到的章节里
所以从那里开始
还有一件关于研究的事情
如果你提前知道你想要的商品
比方说旅行者的靴子
你会发现你没有研究
关于神秘的一个棘手的部分是，很难知道什么研究开启了你真正想要的研究
不在GTNH
将鼠标悬停在研究名称上会告诉你父研究是什么
以及他们在哪个章节
有时可以是直接路径
如果你也看不到先决条件研究
维基中有一份研究备忘单，链接如下
它需要一些弹跳
但最终
你可以找到你需要的所有研究在哪里
以及在哪里解锁
你还可以打开mod选项，让你查看尚未研究的项目的食谱
mod选项
神秘 NEI添加
将军
显示锁定的食谱
但公平的警告
如果它开着，很难判断你到底研究了什么
虽然有用
接下来我会假设你已经有了你需要的所有研究
如果你完成了thaumonicon前四章的大部分内容
你会的
使用神秘取得任何进展
你需要输液祭坛
要使用它，你需要一罐罐香精
要得到这些，你需要一个炼金炉和一些奥术铝（？）
并在魔杖中制作你需要的东西
带上你自己的护目镜
哦等等
你的20容量魔杖太垃圾了
我们会马上解决的
取而代之的是拿起你的地震仪开始游荡
你在寻找节点
它会以明亮的光球出现，直到你靠近
扫描它们，你可以看到它们是由哪些要素组成的
它们大多是最原始的要素
这很好，因为这就是你需要的
晚上搜查能让他们更容易被发现
它们有轻微的光特征类似于蜂巢
你需要至少一个原始要素足够数量来填满你的魔杖
而且越多越好
你不应该走得太远就能得到它
用魔杖右键点击充电
小心不要把节点排空并摧毁它们
这根魔杖坏了
你的首要任务是制作一根足够好的魔杖来获得揭示的护目镜
最终，你可以提前制作其余的vis折扣装备
并阻止自己破网
既然你幸运地用了不锈钢
你可以直接跳到铁帽巨木魔杖
这将vis容量提升到40
如果你有节点保存器研究
将防止你破坏节点
除非你在充电时偷偷摸摸
抓住揭示的护目镜
找到更多节点
这次容易多了
然后开始设计魔法长袍魔法紧身裤和Thaumatry的靴子
最大限度地提高你的手工艺折扣
你需要纺车和一些神秘
是时候谈谈炼金术了
你想从坩埚里得到的第一件事就是nitor
所以把四个火把两个煤和一块发光石扔进去制作它
那是你第一个完美的手艺
再见火
接下来你想要的是大量的平衡碎片和thaumium，神秘贱金属
每个碎片扔四个
用四个空气碎片完成
然后是五个铁锭和五个空气水晶粉
你应该得到四个平衡碎片
五个神秘和五个空气碎片
坩埚里没有多余的香精
它与任何水晶粉末的工作方式相同
碎片按任何顺序排列
如果你厌倦了跑来跑去给你的魔杖充电
你可能会想要一些原始蘑菇
你需要在魔法森林里找到客厅
希望你很久以前就找到了。
或者生物群落指南针可以很容易地引导你
尽可能多地获得
并从任务书中购买它们
一个南瓜、两小堆石灰和一个客厅
给你一个原始的
这是免费的。
喷壶对他也有效
不管你花多少时间做这件事
这比你在节点到节点漫游时花费的要少
有了神秘和所有你需要的东西
你可以开始用炼金炉和一些奥术炼金术
将项目分解为其组件要素
并将其全部储存在罐子里
任何可燃物都可以为其提供燃料
但是铝能让它更快地排出精华。
当你有完美的工艺时，你可以继续使用常规坩埚设置
就像nitor、平衡碎片和thaumium一样
现在是铝和三个煤，三个小堆石粉和一个煤粉
一旦有了精华素
贴上标签
所以我们只接受那种类型的
你可以删除它们
但这可以防止水管让事情变得奇怪
Esentia管道超级愚蠢
但为了我们的目的
直接从蒸馏器里装到罐子里就行了
你也可以给罐子贴上标签。
瞧，恢复必需品以备将来使用
没有必要等待
如果你做几个炼金术构造并把它们粘在坩埚上
现在你有一个完美比例炼金术的系统
只需将你的罐子插入侧面
和宾果邦戈
你还可以并且应该再次升级你的魔杖
这次是缎子缠绕的巨木魔杖
任务是要么（？）缎子更好
所以去做吧
穿上你迷人的长袍和紧身裤，你的护目镜和你的thaumatush靴子
并暂时升级你的最终魔杖
金带大木权杖
你需要那根50容量的魔杖专门用于原始魅力来制作下一根魔杖
这就是魔杖从这里进行的方式
所以习惯吧
有了这个魔杖，你可以开始把节点装在罐子里带回家。
检查研究
缩短你的vis充电时间
并为高级医疗做准备
最后是输液祭坛
这基本上是我们目前的终点
有了这个，神秘的其余部分和所有其他魔法mod都向你开放
更别提游戏史上最棒的动画了
希望你能找到一个愿意和你交换安德珍珠的村民
如果没有，你要等到HV。
这是一个很大的沮丧
因为旅行者的靴子比那早得多
先做那些
为出行变得更加方便而欢欣鼓舞
食谱显示了中心周围的成分
它们不需要井井有条。
但它们确实需要在底座上保持平衡
如果左边有四件物品，就把四件放在右边，以此类推
有些食谱没有完美的平衡
看起来可能有点刺耳
但它们仍然有效
每个配方也有一个稳定值
一旦你拿到奥术算盘
你可以把食谱放在底座上
算盘会告诉你配方的不稳定性
还有你祭坛的稳定性
遗憾的是，你要到MV快结束的时候才能收到这个。
当你可以得到你的第一个高压电路时
在此之前，只是稳定性助推器超载
有很多块可以提高稳定性
他们都告诉你
最简单的方法可能是水银块
它们在你的祭坛下形成对称的图案
你也可以在下面再走几层。
扔下一些骷髅头或蜡烛
只要确保它们的图案是对称的，以获得最大的提升。
一旦稳定下来
列出制作配方
用魔杖右键点击中间的矩阵开始飞船
在旅行者的靴子之后
你想在兔子洞里走多远由你决定
现在你知道怎么进入神秘了
唯一剩下的问题是，为什么
除了解锁其他魔法mod并完成包装之外，事情是这样的
是啊值得
还有旅行者的纳米西装靴
还有和你纳米套装的其余部分搭配的护目镜
这太棒了。
包括我在内的许多玩家都坚持thaumacft修复者（？）
它可以修复遗忘框架
蜜蜂进化的关键早期项目
而飞行药水能创造飞行
是的，你想要这个。
短咬蜜蜂
他们在GTNH中的一切都好得荒谬
我是说一切
他们有足够的理由走到我们在指南中走的那么远
它们是我创造资源的基础
和我自己世界里的发电
好得惊人
如果你想学习如何做蜜蜂
看看Aditya的指南
迄今为止最详尽和有用的GTNH蜜蜂指南
你会很高兴你投资了魔术
如果你想让飞船比我们走得更远
你需要更好的魔杖
哪个三倍的GTNH电子表格有一些惊人的信息
以及关于哪些项目提供最清晰的必需品来源的信息
前往两者的路线链接如下
所以有了神秘的进展
你可以继续使用其他魔术mod
所有这些都有几乎一样好或更好的便利
接下来来点草药怎么样？
Botania有自己的研究分会
我假设你已经完成了相关的内容。
它也有自己的书，Lexica Botania
你应该百分之百地阅读
必须说很棒的mod书
干杯瓦斯奎兹
你不用做神技也能进Botania
但这会有点痛苦
不管怎样，你将从漫步暮色森林开始
寻找含有闪闪发光的蘑菇的洞穴
你会用炼金术把它们变成花
就像大多数事情一样
你收集的越多就越容易滚雪球
所以坚持一会儿
但你也会开启复制它们的方法
也是通过炼金术
或者你可能已经
花瓣药剂师是Botania的手工桌
你首先要做的是纯雏菊
使用药剂师
加满水
放入食谱项目
然后把种子扔进去完成工艺
空手移位右键重复整个食谱
一把纯雏菊就可以了
把它们跳下来，用原木或石头包围每一个
很快它们就会变成活木头和活石头
手里拿着活木头
用几个花瓣和你喜欢的颜色制作你的第一根森林魔杖
现在你准备好摇滚了
活石
我们将在这里加速运行法力生成
好好听讲
制作稀释魔力池
并准备好马上把它扔掉
首先，你必须使用太阳花和夜茄
一个在白天产生魔力，另一个在晚上产生
它们会枯萎，所以要确保物尽其用
在附近放置一个魔力发射器
在绑定模式下shift右键花朵，然后右键发射器以链接它们
你会看到一个绿色对勾，表示链接成功
还有漂亮的粒子效果显示魔力流动
对发射器做同样的操作，将其链接到魔力池
一旦你看到视觉指示
表明你可以通过把钢锭扔进池子来制造魔力钢时
扔下它
然后立即将稀释魔力池换成真正的魔力池
你甚至可以从你的第一批花中抢救一点额外的免费魔力
你需要的下一朵花是火红莲
它可以吃掉可燃物
唯一的困难是来自下界的烈焰花
配合一个30秒的计时器和投掷器
你可以设置一个火红莲来长时间产生魔力
你可以轻松地将相同的设置扩展到一堆火红莲上
长远来看，热爆花
配合永恒之瓮和循环桶进入投掷器（？）
其他工作方式与火红莲设置完全相同
用上一个五分钟的计时器
将会产生大量的魔力
要得到它，你需要符文祭坛
幸运的是，你有神秘注魔
所以这没什么大不了的
你可以将下界石英放入底部有炼金催化器的魔力池中来获得海晶碎片
再做一点研究和合成
它们就是你的了
一旦你拥有了它
在你的魔力池旁边放几个发射器
把它们对准祭坛
用要合成物品右键，将它放到祭坛上
让魔力积累，直到你看到一个漂亮的闪电动画
然后把活石扔在上面
并用森林法杖右键
搞定
你在做符文了
那么为什么要玩植物魔法？
首先
它看起来很酷，是很好的主题装饰
其次是便宜的带等级的玻璃
和出色的GT工具材料
魔力玻璃比同等级的GT玻璃更容易制作
你可以在即将到来的多方块机器中用到它
魔力钢和EV之后的泰拉钢在当前阶段是相当牛逼的工具材料
更不用说植物魔法工具本身了
也是强得疯狂
哦，还有神奇的药水、矿物复制和转化
整个游戏中最长的合成配方
如果你能熬过这一切
最史诗的BOSS战音乐
很难不喜欢
接下来是斯内普教授的魔药课
是时候研究巫术了
它始于一点农活
实际上是把缺水的草锄开，来得到巫术种子
种田
小心曼德拉草
用弩来破坏植物
并立即射死那些小家伙就行了
但如果没有，就做副耳罩
保护好炼药锅、巫师烤炉和陶罐
开始制造所有的"xx之息"
thappings（？）实际上可能是一个问题
你直到现在才需要它们
享受吧
在炼药锅底下点火
用三桶水装满它
把任务书上建议的物品一个一个扔进去
做点转生粉
对着草或者花使用
直到你得到三棵巫术树苗
山梨树、赤杨、山楂树
那你可能需要一点
种些木头，再留几棵树
接下来，你需要巫术祭坛
周围越自然，它的能量越多
所以把不同的树和花都拉满
还有一些其他用来升级祭坛能量的东西
把你自己的头放在上面
还有你用祭坛做的烛台
以及任务中的圣杯
如果你拿了任务奖励里的红石汤
你可以立即升级圣杯，获得优化
短期目标是5450的祭坛能量
如果你缺得太多了
龙蛋会让它一口气充满
尽管龙蛋复杂得需要拆成一个独立任务
先试试更自然的东西
按照任务书找到你真正想要的东西
你需要做个噩梦，然后去到精神世界
做一个水壶
在下面点火
做点沉睡之酿
喝沉睡之酿前喝点飞行药水和夜视药水
你什么都带不进去
而且相信我，你会想速战速决
在躲避怪物的同时，尽可能多地采集纤细棉花
然后随便让哪个怪把你杀了
如果你愿意，这个维度的任务就算完成了
拿上纺车和蒸馏塔
幸运的是，你的法杖容量刚好够合成它们
因为你需要80点Vis的容量
现在你可以制作巫师法袍了
以及最重要的，钻石熏气
这就解锁了你玩巫术模组的主要原因
改变生物群系的药水
对于那些对“欢愉”有特殊要求的蜜蜂来说，这绝对是神器
我有没有说过蜜蜂很棒？
只要搞到生态之书的一页
把任务书建议的物品丢进炼药锅里煮就行
光是这就完全值得你刚才的努力
重申一下，这东西强得离谱
但如果这还不够
你还可以从巫术里搞到一些疯狂的药水
另一个是注魔
那是/home指令的合法替代品
哦还有狼人，你可以变成狼人
还有很多在多人游戏显得很呆的东西
最后，你需要开始血魔法的调谐之石
所以我们和一个不能透露姓名之人一起沉醉于黑暗艺术
德姆斯特朗的一门联合课程
警告在前，发展血魔法肯定会增加你的扭曲
所以如果你打算前期就发展血魔法
做好计划不让这个问题发生
除非你做其他的扭曲研究入魔了
你不会有事的
但你的灵魂已经沦陷
血之祭坛使用来自神秘、巫术以及一些其他物品
并需要聚爆压缩机
除非你在MV后期做出了HV电路板，否则做不出它
除非要做一阶火箭，不然你可能不会做聚爆压缩机
但你应该做聚爆压缩机
因为你只需要两个二重压缩圆石
用火药桶就可以了
血之祭坛是最高六阶的多方块
我们要速通出三阶祭坛
一阶祭坛就只是个方块
最开始，要把它装满血
你需要一把牺牲匕首
是时候放血了
如果你没做好准备，这将是巨大的痛苦与折磨
你可以用各种再生药水
如果这些你都不想用
用烈焰人农场储存的红心来回血
你甚至可能用一些勤劳的蜜蜂提供生命恢复
如果这些都没有，准备好迎接纯粹的痛苦吧
有了足够多的回血，为轻松的街道做准备(?)
做一堆的空白石板
你可以使用漏斗或导管来一次做10个
通过消耗一整个祭坛的LP
设置过滤的EIO导管，只提取所需的符文
这就是最好的制作石板方式
假设你直到获得大量高级符文时才有生命恢复（？）
除非你有三阶祭坛和一堆石板才能做
一大堆的石板
当然，还要做一阶血魔法宝珠
一旦你有了它
拿着宝珠按鼠标右键进行绑定
然后把它放到祭坛，让它吸点血
你现在就有了一个LP网络
见解印记会告诉你你有多少LP
还有一堆很酷的印记
需要八个气血符文将祭坛升级到二阶
在祭坛里放入你的二阶宝珠
还要20个气血符文将祭坛升到三阶
每个气血符文要四个空白石板，总共112个石板
那是在你获得能提升获得LP效率的符文之前
祭坛每升一级，能多做一级石板
你会想要一堆二阶的
还有一些三阶的
除了你升级符文所需的那些
是的，你需要大量的血
3阶祭坛还需要血腥神秘块
我希望你早点做了那些
三阶宝珠需要3万LP
所以速度符文可能会让你掉血
除非你也做出了一些增强和容量符文
无论如何，在制作三阶宝珠之前，你需要做点符文
但你无论如何都需要钛
所以你现在没办法做它
这意味着你有时间在HV后期前制作升级符文
也意味着你也有时间做一点血魔法炼金术
经过更多的研究
你可以制作炼金术士化学套装
这东西有很多非常有用的配方
但现在你要的是炼金术原料
简单催化剂
强化催化剂
神圣粉末
暗黑粉末
火焰粉末
效能粉末
以太元素
泥土粉末
液之粉末
还有一些其他的
但有了这些
你可以自由地做出重大决定
牺牲或献祭
你会在这个血魔法阶段里呆一会儿
所以一些牺牲符文是值得的
它们会大大加快献血的速度
如果你打算这样做，考虑一下玻璃牺牲匕首
如果你打算做苦难之井
而它是你无论如何都会做的
你要做献祭符文
问题是你需要一个4阶祭坛
而这需要你再发展很多神秘
非常多
危险的那种
这样看来，任务书的引导做得很好
它们开始有点重叠
变得有点复杂
所以我们可能在之后指南的某个时候又讲一次魔法
如果你感兴趣，弹幕扣1
疯狂框架（？）
如果你已经开始养蜂了，也许可以做出来
蜜蜂育种的神器
苦难之井
能提供无限的LP
约束工具
无限耐久，能一键清空矿脉
约束装甲
让你几乎无敌
看起来也帅
能量爆破器（？）
能进行毁灭性的能量攻击
如果你能把它们组合起来
全自动血魔法坠星的收集
使用魔镜进行跨维度物品传输
足够的物品传输速率来处理获得的物品
和应用神秘
数字化源质存储和自动化
魔法太好用了
而且被低估了太多
GTNH表面上是一个科技包
但它不止科技
随着你制造的铝增加，你有很多东西可以探索
修复发电系统
准备好迎接MV要遇到的野兽
第七集见